

Senior Full-stack and Blockchain Developer

Daniil Aslanov

Address : Kalnishevskogo 7, ap 1206

Birthday: June 5, 1996

Phone: (+380) 960-929-493

GitHub: https://github.com/Topdev0104

Skype: live:.cid.ef18a5a6e2b9dbe6

Job: Remote, Full-stack, Blockchain, Full-time, Any time zone

Front-end Developer

Full-stack Developer

Blockchain Developer

Let me introduce myself

I am a senior full-stack and blockchain developer with 5 years of strong skills and mature experience in modern software development.

I am familiar with MERN Stack and NFT ecosystem, specially NFT Minting DApps, NFT Marketplace and Staking) project.

My Main Skills

| Blockchain | 95% |
|-------------------------|------|
| Solidity | 100% |
| Smart Contract | 95% |
| NFT Ecosystem | 100% |
| Web3.js, Ether.js | 100% |
| Truffle, Remix, Hardhat | 100% |
| MERN Stack | 100% |

Work Experience

Front-end Developer, April 2019 ~ October 2019

- Created fully responsive web pages using Material-UI, Bootstrap and Styled-component.

Full-stack Developer, January 2020 ~ August 2020

- Worked in the MERN Stack project to build the P2P Marketplace.
- Developed the project for contract management using MERN Stack.

Blockchain Developer, November 2020 - April 2021

- Developed smart contracts for decentralized token platform on EVM.
- Developed the several NFT Minting DApps on Ethereum network.
- Developed front-end by React.js and implement smart contract integration using web3.js and ether.js

Education

Kyiv National University of Trade and Economics

- Bachelor of Computer Science (BCompSc)
- July 2015 April 2019

Language

Ukrainian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Russian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Fluent